Hello friends, today we will talk about HDFC
's Koti Suraksha Plan,
what is this plan and why should you take it,
how many
policies can you take if the bag gets fractured and more than that is the
defending only
if there is income loss in an accident and you cannot walk,
you can not take back if there is income
loss, there is a
bodyguard which will definitely protect you and
your family, will protect you,
if there is income loss,
hospitalization expenses will definitely be there
but at the same time it
also generates income for you, forward
and for more details contact me tomorrow,
we will help you and taking up this
HDFC Ego